https://www.efca.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy addresses the Evangelical Free Church of America’s ("EFCA") policies and practices with respect to personally-identifiable information collected by the EFCA through EFCA websites. Protecting your privacy is important to us. We want you to understand what information we collect, how we use it, and the steps we take to protect that information.
Information we collect
There are four different ways we collect information from visitors on EFCA websites. From online:
Requests for information (i.e. E-mail newsletters, contact forms, etc.)
Requests for materials from our organization
Donations
Event registrations
At the instruction of you, the constituent or donor, we collect personally-identifiable information on the forms we receive from you and in connection with the subscriptions, registrations or donations you conduct with us. This information may include, among other things, your first and last name, address, city, state, ZIP/postal code, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date, bank or credit union account information, and other information that permits us to contact you either electronically or by other means, to maintain and store this information through the use of these identifying items, and process event registrations or the requested donations as instructed by you, the constituent or donor to perform financial registrations or donations.
Information the website collects automatically
The EFCA uses standard non-personally identifiable information about a constituent or donor’s computer including IP address and browser version.
Access to personal information
You may request to review, update, or have deleted any personal information collected from you by the EFCA. To do so, please contact us via one of the options listed below asking to review or update your personal information, or to have us delete your personal information. We reserve the right, however, to retain personal information as necessary to comply with federal and state laws.
Children’s privacy
We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under age thirteen. If you believe a child under the age of thirteen has submitted personally-identifiable information to us, please contact us via one of the options listed below providing details about the submission of the data and we will delete the personally-identifiable information from our databases.
Information we disclose
We do not disclose any personally-identifiable information about our constituents and donors or former constituents and donors to anyone outside of our organization, except as permitted or required by law. For example, personally-identifiable information may be disclosed to third parties providing essential services to us who have contracted to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information, or to law enforcement personnel pursuant to proper authority.
Response and security
We limit access to personally-identifiable information about our constituents and former constituents and donors to those employees who need to know that information to perform their job responsibilities. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard the nonpublic personal information of our constituents and donors and former constituents and donors.
Linking
Any third party websites that you visit as a result of linking, searching, or surfing from our website may collect and record data about you. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by EFCA websites and by the EFCA.
Links are provided for your convenience only. The EFCA does not control the websites listed and assumes no liability or responsibility for them, including any content or services provided to you. You should not consider any link to or from another website as an endorsement of that website by the EFCA unless expressly stated.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or if you have concerns about the way we collect and use your personally-identifiable information, please contact us:
EFCA, Attn: Webmaster, 901 E. 78th St., Minneapolis, MN 55420
(800) 745-2202 or (952) 854-1300
webmaster@efca.org
Changes to our privacy policy
We may amend our Privacy Policy at any time. When you visit our websites, you agree to the terms of the current Privacy Policy as found on the web site. We encourage you to check the Privacy Policy regularly to remain informed of any changes.
Governing law
This Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Minnesota, United States of America.
This Privacy Policy was last updated April 2018.
All rights reserved. Read our privacy policy and copyright policy.
